const qBank = [
  {
    question: "What is Oyolah's full name?   ",
    answers: [
      "Oyolah Mustapha",
      "Oyolah Mustapha Kamara",
      "Athens Oyolah Kamara",
      "Oyolah Mustapha Kargbo",
    ],
    correct: "Oyolah Mustapha Kamara",
    questionId: "099099",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Oyolah's best friend ?",
    answers: ["Ablel", "Lamin", "Omar", "Abass"],
    correct: "Ablel",
    questionId: "183452",
  },
  {
    question: "Pick the odd ?",
    answers: ["Dimitra", "Emily", "Anastacia", "Dimitris"],
    correct: "Dimitris",
    questionId: "267908",
  },
  {
    question: "What's the greek word for Greece?",
    answers: ["Ελληνικό", "αγελάδα", "Ελλάδα", "Ελληνικά"],
    correct: "Ελλάδα",
    questionId: "333247",
  },
  {
    question: "who is the first Prime Minister of Greece?",
    answers: [
      "Mitsotakis",
      "Georgios Kountouriotis",
      "Alexandros",
      "Mavromichalis",
    ],
    correct: "Alexandros Mavrokordatos",
    questionId: "496293",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a province in Greece?",
    answers: ["Attica", "Chalkidiki", "Chania", "Omonia"],
    correct: "Omonia",
    questionId: "588909",
  },
  {
    question: "how man letters are in the greek alphbets?",
    answers: ["26", "24", "25", "27"],
    correct: "24",
    questionId: "648452",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the first book of the Old Testament?",
    answers: ["Genesis", "Exodus", "Leviticus", "Numbers"],
    correct: "Genesis",
    questionId: "786649",
  },
  {
    question: "Greece is part of this Organization except ?",
    answers: ["NATO", "EU", "G-20", "World-Bank"],
    correct: "G-20",
    questionId: "839754",
  },
  {
    question: "Which are the highest group of christians in greece?",
    answers: ["Roman Catholic", "Orthodox ", "Protestant", "	Anglican"],
    correct: "Orthodox",
    questionId: "98390",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Parthenon was built in honor of which wise and well-known Greek goddess?",
    answers: ["Athena", "Artemis", "Aphrodite", "Hera"],
    correct: "Athena",
    questionId: "1071006",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the largest island in Greece?",
    answers: ["Crete", "Lesbos", "Rhodes", "Chíos"],
    correct: "Crete",
    questionId: "1174154",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a very popular sport in Greece?",
    answers: ["Basket Ball", "Vollay Ball", "Horse Race", "Soccer"],
    correct: "Soccer",
    questionId: "1226535",
  },
  {
    question: "How would one say goodbye in Spanish?",
    answers: ["Adiós", " Hola", "Au Revoir", "Salir"],
    correct: "Adiós",
    questionId: "1310938",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the largest organ of the human body?",
    answers: ["Skin", "Heart", "large Intestine", "Liver"],
    correct: "Skin",
    questionId: "1436873",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the official language of Greece?",
    answers: ["Greek", "English", "Turkish", "Albania"],
    correct: "Greek",
    questionId: "1515110",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Athens' port?",
    answers: ["Aegina", "Corfu", "Piraeus", "Keramoti"],
    correct: "Piraeus",
    questionId: "1642728",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does the 'S' stand for in the abbreviation SIM, as in SIM card? ",
    answers: ["Subscriber", "Single", "Secure", "Solid"],
    correct: "Subscriber",
    questionId: "1747256",
  },
  {
    question: "In the Greek language, what does 'kalimera' mean?",
    answers: ["Good Evening", "Morning", "Good Morning", "Morning Good"],
    correct: "Good Morning",
    questionId: "1822532",
  },
  {
    question: "Greece is part of which union?",
    answers: [
      "European Union",
      "Miner's Union",
      "Soviet Union",
      "Greeker Union",
    ],
    correct: "European Union",
    questionId: "195075",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the capital of Greece?",
    answers: ["Albania", "Thessaloniki", "Piraeus", "Athens"],
    correct: "Athens",
    questionId: "2019778",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Greece's national airline called?",
    answers: [
      "Greece International",
      "Olympic Air",
      "Ellinikon",
      "National Greece Airline",
    ],
    correct: "Olympic Air",
    questionId: "2134343",
  },
  {
    question: "How many boys live in 48 Isavron ?",
    answers: ["17", "36", "10", "20"],
    correct: "17",
    questionId: "2210799",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the biggest company in greece ?",
    answers: ["OTE", "Alpha Bank", "Per Hour", "Olympic Air"],
    correct: "Alpha Bank",
    questionId: "2379831",
  },
  {
    question: "Which country is not part of the European Union ?",
    answers: ["Norway", "Holland", "Finland", "Latvia"],
    correct: "Norway",
    questionId: "2426418",
  },
  {
    question: "List of West Africa countries except ?",
    answers: ["Guinea", "Sierra Leone", "The Gambia", "Tanzania"],
    correct: "Tanzania",
    questionId: "2510086",
  },
  {
    question: "Oyolah's world favorite country ?",
    answers: ["UK", "Tanzania", "Thailand", "Nigeria"],
    correct: "Tanzania",
    questionId: "2685745",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the capital city of Sierra Leone ?",
    answers: ["Freetown", "Conakry", "Lagos", "Monrovia"],
    correct: "Freetown",
    questionId: "2796884",
  },
  {
    question: "what is the landmark of Freetown ?",
    answers: [
      "Law Court",
      "Cotton Tree",
      "Queen Elizabeth 2",
      "Fourah Bay College",
    ],
    correct: "Cotton Tree",
    questionId: "2838900",
  },
  {
    question: "Freetown in Sierra Leone got it name from ?",
    answers: ["British", "Portuguese", "Free Slaves", "Travellers"],
    correct: "Free Slaves",
    questionId: "298060",
  },
  {
    question: "The name Sierra Leone is originated from which language ?",
    answers: ["English", "Greek", "Portuguese", "Spanish"],
    correct: "Portuguese",
    questionId: "3096579",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the meaning of Sierra Leone ?",
    answers: ["Beautiful Land", "Lion Mountain", "Flat Land", "Land of Water"],
    correct: "Lion Mountain",
    questionId: "3182461",
  },
  {
    question: "How many countries are in Africa ?",
    answers: ["55", "54", "60", "48"],
    correct: "54",
    questionId: "3239112",
  },
  {
    question: "How many countries are in Europe ?",
    answers: ["44", "46", "42", "48"],
    correct: "44",
    questionId: "3318503",
  },
  {
    question: "Which country in Africa has the highest mountain ?",
    answers: ["Tanzania", "Ugandan", "Rwanda", "Burundi"],
    correct: "Tanzania",
    questionId: "3410327",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Lake Victoria the largest natural lake in the world is located in ?",
    answers: ["West Africa", "East Africa", "North Africa", "South Africa"],
    correct: "East Africa",
    questionId: "3542596",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of this English word id from Greek language ?",
    answers: ["Synopsis", "Interference", "Dispute", "Victoria"],
    correct: "Synopsis",
    questionId: "3667517",
  },
  {
    question: "Athens have three line of metro colored ?",
    answers: [
      "Green Red Pink",
      "Green Red Blue",
      "Blue Green Orange",
      "Orange Pink Red",
    ],
    correct: "Green Red Blue",
    questionId: "3791672",
  },
  {
    question: "Oyolah's Favorite teacher in school ?",
    answers: ["K. Chrisou", "K. Lianoulopoulou", "k. Papagianni", "K. Manuka"],
    correct: "K. Manuka",
    questionId: "3893585",
  },
  {
    question: "Greek word that must be added to the greek national anthem ?",
    answers: ["γαμώ", "μαλάκα", "αυνανίζομαι", "κώλος"],
    correct: "μαλάκα",
    questionId: "3913430",
  },
  {
    question: "The most use word in the greek language ?",
    answers: ["μαλάκα", "Καλός", "μπράβο", "αγάπη"],
    correct: "μαλάκα",
    questionId: "4049121",
  },
  {
    question: "what do Oyolah like so much ?",
    answers: ["Girls", "Computers", "Food", "Movies"],
    correct: "Girls",
    questionId: "4150746",
  },
  {
    question: "Oyolah's favorite programming language ?",
    answers: ["Java", "Python", "Javascript", "C++"],
    correct: "Javascript",
    questionId: "4235063",
  },
  {
    question: "The name of Oyolah's Mother ?",
    answers: ["Yankai", "Nawal", "Aminata", "Fatima"],
    correct: "Yankai",
    questionId: "4321002",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the big boss of SMAN organization ?",
    answers: ["Dimitra Big", "K.Yannis", "Dimitra Small", "K.Mitsotakis"],
    correct: "K.Yannis",
    questionId: "4442286",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which phrase doesn't make sense in English as what it means, but does in greek ?",
    answers: ["Go to school", "Take a shower", "Hit the nail", "Yes i do"],
    correct: "Take a shower",
    questionId: "4564430",
  },
  {
    question: "the greek word υπνοδωμάτιο means ?",
    answers: ["Room", "rooms", "Bedroom", "bedrooms"],
    correct: "Bedroom",
    questionId: "4630606",
  },
  {
    question: "Greece won the euro cup when ?",
    answers: ["2003", "2004", "2001", "2000"],
    correct: "2004",
    questionId: "4795960",
  },
  {
    question: "Greece is best known for ?",
    answers: ["Gold export", "Olive", "Diamond", "Tourism"],
    correct: "Tourism",
    questionId: "4811162",
  },
  {
    question: "The best soccer player in the world as of my opinion ?",
    answers: [
      "Chistiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Andres Inesta",
      "Eden Hazard",
    ],
    correct: "Chistiano Ronaldo",
    questionId: "4982981",
  },
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
